A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), Laurance S. Rockefeller General Files, 1992-1996, RG 43 FA1325
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Medicine, 1992-1996; 26
  - Hospitals - St. John's Hospital, Jackson, WY, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Hospitals - Society of New York, New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 18-19)
  - Hospitals - Society of New York, New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center - Printed Matter, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Mental Health - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health - C. G. Jung Institute of San Francisco, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health - The Lifwynn Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health - Mind and Life Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health - Thompson, Angela M., 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Narcotics - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Narcotics - Phoenix House, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Narcotics - United States Government - President's Drug Advisory Council, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- N, O, P - General, 1992-1996; 27
  - N - O - P - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Philanthropy, 1992-1996; 28
  - Philanthropy - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Philanthropy - New Concepts in Philanthropy Fund, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Philanthropy - Foundation for New Era Philanthropy, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
  - Philanthropy - Foundation for New Era Philanthropy - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Philanthropy - Foundation for New Era Philanthropy (Box 50A, Folder 1-7)
- Politics, 1992-1996; 29
  - Politics - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
  - Common Cause, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Galbraith, Van, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Giuliani, Rudy, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - House Majority Trust, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - New York Republican County Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - New York Republican State Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Roundtable, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Presidential Roundtable - 2017:FA1325:010 - The President's Club Cufflinks (Box 2017:FA1325:010)
  - Presidential Roundtable - 2017:FA1325:011 - Richard Nixon Commemorative Coin (Box 2017:FA1325:011)
  - Republican Mainstream Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Republican National Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - 2017:FA1325:014 - Republican Convention 1992 - Finance Committee Medal LSR (Box 2017:FA1325:014)
  - 2017:FA1325:015 - GOP TV - "Rising Tide", Republican Gala Special, Ronald Reagan Celebration, 1994 February 3; VHS, 60 minutes (Box 2017:FA1325:015)
  - Republican Senate House Dinner, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Ripon Society, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, John D. IV, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Larry, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rosenbaum, Richard M., 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Voinovich, George V., 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Voinovich, George V. - 2017:FA1325:012 - Governor George Voinovich: Working Harder, Working Smarter, 1992-1996; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:012)
  - Wilson, Pete, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Contributions - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 51, Folder 10-16)
  - 2017:FA1325:013 - Bernadette Castro, United States Senate Race, 1994; VHS, 9 minutes (Box 2017:FA1325:013)
- Population, 1992-1996; 30
  - Population - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Population Action International, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Population Council, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Abortion - A -Z, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Abortion - National Abortion Rights Action League, New York State Affiliate, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Abortion - National Abortion Rights Action League Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- R - General, 1992-1996; 31
  - R - Miscellaneous - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Race Relations - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Real Estate, 1992-1996; 32
  - Real Estate - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Caneel Bay, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - The Enterprise Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Estate Fountain River Wells vs. Rockefeller, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills, 1979-1993 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Greenrock (Box 52, Folder 15-20)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Employees - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Finances-Audit Budget, 1994-1997 (Box 53, Folder 3-5)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - General, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Memos, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Special Projects, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - Special Projects - LSR Approvals, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 10-13)
  - Greenrock - Operations Building, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Little Dix Bay (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Little Dix Bay - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1992-1996 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Mauna Kea - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Hills - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Pocantico Hills - The Park, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Pocantico Hills - Parcel B-18, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - Emperor Akihito and Empress Michico of Japan, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - Guest House, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Pocantico Hills - Playhouse A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Group - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Rock Resorts, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller and Assoc. Realty - La Jolla Spectrum Projects, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller and Assoc. Realty - Malibu Canyon Business Park, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller and Assoc. Realty - Projects-Huntington Management Corporation, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller and Assoc. Realty - Ridgemoor Projects, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Recreation, 1992-1996; 33
  - Recreation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Religion, 1992-1996; 34
  - Religion - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 1-11)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 12-13)
  - A New American Place, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Atrium Society, 1992-1996 (Box 56, Folder 1-4)
  - The Buddhist Ray, 1992-1996 (Box 56, Folder 5-7)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ International, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Center for a Post-Modern World, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Choosing Our Future, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - Conlon, James A., 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Dharma, Sangha, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Diocese of Oakland, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Dungkar Gompa Society, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Emissary Foundation International, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Fellowship in Prayer, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Foundation for Co-Creation, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Foundation for Conscious Evolution, 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Foundation for Shamanic Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 1-4)
  - Foundation for Shamanic Studies - 2017:FA1325:016 - Journey to Tuva, 1994; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:016)
  - Fox, Matthew, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Fund for the Enhancement of the Human Spirit, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
  - The Healthcare Chaplaincy (Hospital Chaplaincy), 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 8-10)
  - 2017:FA1325:017 - The Hospital Chaplaincy, VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:017)
  - Holohform Research, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 11-13)
  - International Transpersonal Association, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Kuroda Institute for the Study of Buddhism and Human Values, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Lachane, Albert J., 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Laitty Lodge Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Lex Hixon, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Mother Tessa - Spiritual Life Institute (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Peale Center for Christian Living, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Sacred Words, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Sanctuary Project, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Samaya Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - San Luis Valley Tibetan Project, 1992-1996 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Spiritual Life Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Tanager Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - John Templeton Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 60, Folder 4-7)
  - John Templeton Foundation - 2017:FA1325:018 - Body, Mind and Spirit, 1995; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:018)
  - John Templeton Foundation - 2017:FA1325:019 - The Question Is, VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:019)
  - Tibet House, 1992-1996 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Trinity Forum, 1992-1996 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Trinity Forum, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Upaya, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - The Upaya Chapter of the Tiep Hein Order, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
  - World Council of Churches, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Zen Studies Society, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Churches - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
  - Churches - The Brick Presbyterian Church, New York, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Churches - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Churches - First Congressional Church, Woodstock, VT, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Churches - Grace Cathedral, San Francisco, CA, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Churches - Riverside Church, New York, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Churches - St. John's Episcopal Church, Jackson, WY, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Churches - St. Paul's Episcopal Church, San Miguel de Allende, Mexico, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Churches - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Missions - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Missions - New York City Mission Society, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Rockefeller Family, 1992-1996; 35
  - Rockefeller Family - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Airplanes - Wayfarer, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 9-16)
  - Rockefeller Family Office - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller Family Office - Awards - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Awards - Scenic Hudson, 1992-1996 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Awards - Scenic Hudson - 2017:FA1325:020 - The Rockefeller's Honor Earth, 1994; VHS, 3 minutes and 14 seconds. (Box 2017:FA1325:020)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Trusts, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Restricted material
  - Trusts - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jr. and Mark F. Rockefeller, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 2-3)
  - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 5-9)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, John D. - Michigan Hill, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., Jr. (Abby Aldrich), 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller, Larry, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, Larry - Beaverkill Project, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 14-15)
  - Rockefeller, Larry - Beaverkill Project - OSI Reorganization, 1992-1996 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1992-1996; 36
  - LSR - A - K, 1992-1996 (Box 64, Folder 3-11)
  - LSR - L - S, 1992-1996 (Box 65, Folder 1-11)
  - LSR - T - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller: The Woman in the Family, 1993 November (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Akaka, Rev. Abraham Kahikina and Mrs., 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B., 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Articles - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Automobiles, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Awards - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Awards - American Psychosomatic Society, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Awards - Citizen's Committee for New York City, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 12-15)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Background Material, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Recipients, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Gold Medal Photograph and Inscription, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Congressional Record, 1991 October 1 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Congressional Record, 1990 May 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Photos of LSR by Larry French, 1990 Spring (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Letters in Support of LSR, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Recipients of CGM Replica LSR Letter, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Thank You Letters to LSR for Gift of Replicas of Gold Medal, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Letters of Congratulations to LSR, 1990 May (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Response to Congratulation Letters, 1991 September-October (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Letter of Thanks to President George H. W. Bush, 1991 September 30 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Acceptance Speech, 1991 September 27 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - President Bush Speech (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Press Release, 1991 September 27 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Thank You Letter to N. Castro, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Guest List Gold Medal Presentation, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Travel Schedule, 1991 September 27 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Press Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Letter to President George H. W. Bush, 1990 May 30 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Thank You Letter to George D. Taylor, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Copies of NC Thank You Letters, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Nash Castro Statement Before Sub-Committee, 1990 May 4 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - LSR Thank You Letter - Draft, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Sponsors of House Resolution No. 3625, 1990 March 19 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Thank You Letters - List, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Thank You Letters (Copies), 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Awards - Congressional Gold Medal - Thank You Letters - Lists, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
  - Awards - National Georgraphic Society, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Awards - National Park Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Lecture, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Princeton, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - LSR Itinerary, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Dinner at Lowrie House, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Press Cuttings, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Luncheon Remarks, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Congratulation Letters to LSR, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Congratulations on Lectures and Remarks, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - LSR Lecture Faculty Panel, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - President Shapiro and Faculty Panel Alumni Day - Tapes, 1991 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Speech Luncheon Remarks Questions and Answers, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 16-17)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Princeton Master, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award - Society of Mayflower Descendents in the State of New York, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Biography, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Boats - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Boats - Evening Star, 1987-1996 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Books, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Birthdays and Gifts, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Book - Biography, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews, 1994 March 30 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - Conservation, 1993 December 16 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - Education, 1993 July 23 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - Family, 1993 August 17 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - MSKCC, 1994 January 24 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - Resorts, 1993 November 18 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Biography - Seitel Interviews - Venture Capital, 1993 October 13 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Branscombe, Mrs. Robert F. (Jean), 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Bubela, Peter and Mrs. (Patricia), 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Canning Book, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Consultants - Stern, Alexis, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Castro, Nash, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Special Funding Projects, Dr. Deepak Chopra, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Consultants, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Consultants - Binder, Wade, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Consultants - Diamond, Henry, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Consultants - Swimme, Dr. Brian, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Consultants - Thompson, Keith, 1992-1996 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Debevoise, Thomas M., 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - Family Christmas Luncheon, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - Library of Congress, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - National Geographic Society, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - Princeton, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Employees - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Financial Review, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - French, John III and Mrs., 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - French, Lawrence, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - French, Robert W. and Mrs. Jenny, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 14-15)
  - Gifts - Andrews, Valerie, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Gifts - Dawit, Seble, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Gifts - Feuerstein, George, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Gifts - Gift Review Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Gifts - Lightfoot - Klein, Hanny, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Gifts - McAllister, Joann, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - Needleman, Jacob, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Gifts - Oubre, Alondra Y., 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Gifts - Swenson, Lee, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Gifts - Thompson, Keith, 1992-1996 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Gifts - Warnock, Kathleen, 1992-1996 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - Weir, Roger, 1992-1996 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Giving Program - General, 1992-1996 (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - Giving Program - 1995 A - Z (Box 71, Folder 5-12)
  - Giving Program - 1994 A - Z (Box 72, Folder 1-9)
  - Giving Program - 1993 A - Z (Box 73, Folder 1-5)
  - Giving Program - 1992 A - N (Box 74, Folder 6-10)
  - Giving Program - 1992 O - Z (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
  - Goodwin, Neva R., 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Growald, Paul and Eileen, 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Hickenbottom, Randy and Jennifer, 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Hitchcock, Ethan Allen, 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Holtzman, Sheila, 1992-1996 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Insurance, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 9-10)
  - Insurance Summary, 1994-1996 (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
  - Interviews - Seitel, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 13-16)
  - Interviews - Material from LBJ, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Investments - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Investments - Messinger Music Company, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
  - Investments - Optima Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 4-7)
  - Investments - Securities Summary, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 8-10)
  - Investments - Pomeroy, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 11-13)
  - Invitations (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Invitations - Invitations to Speak - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Invitations - Jenrette, Richard H., 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 4-6)
  - Kert, Bernice, 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Lanier, Sidney, 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 8-12)
  - Lincoln School, 1992-1996 (Box 76, Folder 13-17)
  - Lincoln School, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Loans, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Matousek, Otakar, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - McDermott, Dr. Robert A. and Ellen Dineen, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Moore, Dean and Mary French, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Olds, Dr. Glenn A., 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - O'Neill, George D., 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Personal Services, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Personnel - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Petrie, Milton and Carol, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Portfolio Summary, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Property - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Property - Cornwall House, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Property - Hawaii, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Property - JY Ranch - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 15-16)
  - Property - JY Ranch - General, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Property - JY Ranch, 1963-1991 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Property - JY Ranch - 1994 Budget (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Property - JY Ranch - 1995 Budget (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Employees, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 21-22)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Long, Richard, 1992-1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Visits (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - 1995 President Clinton (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Property - JY Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1992-1996 (Box 78, Folder 5-15)
  - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue, 1992-1996 (Box 79, Folder 1-7)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills, 1972-1996 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kent House, 1992-1996 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Leases - Abby and Charles Caulkin Ingrid R. Rockefeller, 1992-1996 (Box 80, Folder 5)